Guide to the Administrative Files of the Dean of the School of Education, Daniel E. Griffiths 1948-1985 (Bulk 1965-1983) RG 26.0.1 RG.26.0.1
New York University Archives
- Griffiths Container List
  - Chase: "Our Changing Schools of Education", 1966 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Christmas Cards, 1967 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Cincinnati School Survey (Oscar Chute), undated (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Closed Circuit, 1966 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Collective Negotiations: Proposed Publication, undated (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Computers, Ideas for, 1967-1968 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Division of A&S Conference on Collective Negotiations, 1967 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Contemporary Problems in Education: Interdisiplinary Analysis, undated (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - College Bound Corporation, 1967-1968 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - College Federal Agency Council, undated (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Conant: The Education of American Teachers - Reactions by the Deans, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 328 1
  - Cooperative Review Service Study: Desegregation of Buffalo Public Schools, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Counseling, 1966 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Craig Proposal for Graduate Fellowships, 1966 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Craig: Editorial Research for School of Education Litterature, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Ad Hoc Committee to Study the Functioning of the Faculty Council, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Ad Hoc Committee to Study Structures of the Faculty, 1962-1963 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Committee for the Self-Study, Special faculty Meeting, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Continuing Education, 1962-1964 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Curriculum, 1953-1963 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Memorandum to the Committee on Discipline, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Faculty - Student Policies, 1966-1967 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Committee on International Education, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Cuervavoca, Mexico CIDOC, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - College Federal Agency Council, undated (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Faculty and Administrators, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Cerberus, undated (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Deans Council, 1967-1968 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Deans Council Meetings, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Deans Council - Minutes, 1961-1967 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - "Deliberative" Committee, Dean Gitlow, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Ford Foundation, Mr. Reuban Frodin, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - New York University Head Start Advisory Committee, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - M.A.T., 1966 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - Mission of Other Schools, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Proposals - Mediation, Oceanhill, Brownsville, 1967-1968 (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Westinghouse and Bronx Study, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - WMCA Tape - Interview, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - Annual Reports from Dept. Chairmen, 1961-1962 (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report - WAA, 1959-1960 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report, 1952-1959 (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Annual Report to Chancellor, 1949-1954 (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Report to Comm. on Expert and Consulting Services rendered by Sch. Of Ed, 1938-1939 (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Edgemont Board of Education, 1959-1963 (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - Encyclopedia of Educational Research, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 35)
  - DEG, 1961-1969 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 329 9
  - Ed. Assns. And High Schools, 1965 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - School of Education, 1965 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - NYU - Non School of Education, 1965 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Colleges and Universities, 1965 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Personal, 1965 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - In-Basket Ideas, 1963 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - In-Basket Material, 1964 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Interstate, 1961-1968 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Integration Committee, 1966 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Inventory of DEG Material, 1961 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Invitations declined, 1962-1968 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Iternary - Europe (summer), 1966 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Kleinman's Class, 1964 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Culbertson Correspondence, 1957-1968 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Annual Report - DGS Project, 1958 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1957-1968 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - Board Meetings, 1966 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - UCEA Board of Trustees Meeting, 1966 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - Board Meetings, 1962-1965 (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - Newsletters, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 331 5
  - Support Commission, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Gallatin College Project, 1961-1962 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Gold Tournament, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Grace, Alonzo G., 1967 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Grace Reports and Other Basic Documents, undated (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Grading and Evaluation, 1964 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Academy for Civil Rights, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Group Attitudes Corp; H&K Marketing Services Corp, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Guidance Counselors Symposium, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - NYU's Harlem Seminars - Dean Russell Smith, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Hebrew Technical Institute, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965, 1965-1967 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Hilsinger Meeting, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Honorary Degrees, Recommendations for, 1966 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Hopson, Anna Lee - Confidential, 1964 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Institutional Services Meeting - Berezin, LK, Brecket, Smith, Bloom, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Intergrative Education, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - Interdepartmental Courses, 1966 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Internship Proposal, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - Leadership for Education, undated (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Liberal Arts, 1963 (Box 122, Folder 22)
  - Lindback Awards, 1965-1966 (Box 122, Folder 23)
  - Lutheran Church in America, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 24)
  - McRel, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 25)
  - Maas Essay Award, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 26)
  - Mail Delivery Complaints, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 27)
  - Mailing Lists, 1965 (Box 122, Folder 28)
  - Manuscripts, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 29)
  - Masters Degree for ITTP students, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 30)
  - Masters Degree Program, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 31)
  - Meeting with President Hester, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 32)
  - Memos to Faculty, Div. And Dept. Heads, Deans, Etc, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 33)
  - Middle States Conference, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 34)
  - Middle States Association, 1963 (Box 122, Folder 35)
  - MIND Inc., 1968 (Box 122, Folder 36)
  - Minnesota Superintendents, 1966 (Box 122, Folder 37)
  - Meeting with Seeley, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 38)
  - Mayors Panel Framework for Change, 1967 (Box 122, Folder 39)
  - Univ. Comm. On Decentralization, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 40)
  - Mexico City Trip, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 41)
  - Model School, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 332 3
  - Music Education Meeting, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Music Education Meeting: re Bain Report, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Music Education, 1967-1968 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Music Courses in GSAS, WSC, and S/E, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Meeting with Enoch Light, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - NAACP Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1965 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - NASSP Administration Internship in Secondary School Improvement, undated (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Education, 1965 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - National Advisory Council on Education, 1963 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - National Council for Social Studies, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - NIMH Proposal, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - NCATE - General, 1960-1966 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - National Teachers Examination, 1963 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - NCATE Report, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - National Security Policy and Administration, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corp Training Program, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - NYU Camp, 1962-1967 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - NYU Financial Report, 1962-1963 (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - NYU Projections of Financial Status, 1965 (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - Norfolk: Virginia State College, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - Nurse Education, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 22)
  - Occupational Therapy Survey of Accredidation, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 23)
  - England, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 24)
  - Exam for Administrative Theory Seminar, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 25)
  - Dodson Statement to Kerner Comm., 1968 (Box 123, Folder 26)
  - Retreat of Deans, 1964 (Box 123, Folder 27)
  - Deans Group - Activities Report, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 28)
  - Deans Group - Two Day Session, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 29)
  - Deans Meeting, 1963 (Box 123, Folder 30)
  - Development of an Instructional System in Educational Administration, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 31)
  - Diamond Jubilee, 1965 (Box 123, Folder 32)
  - Directory, 1967-1968 (Box 123, Folder 33)
  - Distinguished Professorships, 1964 (Box 123, Folder 34)
  - Drama Courses, 1965-1966 (Box 123, Folder 35)
  - Deans Group - Agenda, 1965-1970 (Box 123, Folder 36)
  - Deans Group - Minutes, 1964-1968 (Box 123, Folder 37)
  - Departmental Chairman meetings, 1964-1967 (Box 123, Folder 38)
  - Deans Memo, 1967-1969 (Box 123, Folder 39)
  - Departmental of Secondary Education, 1962-1964 (Box 123, Folder 40)
  - Seminar in State Music Supervision, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 41)
  - Departmental of Vocational Education, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 42)
  - Departmental of Home Economics Education, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 43)
  - Division of Educational Administration, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 44)
  - Eastern States Assoc. for Teacher Education, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 45)
  - Application for Support Under Various Sections of the Higher Ed. Fac. Act, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 46)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 47)
  - Report to the Faculty, 1967 (Box 123, Folder 48)
  - Brendan Sexton, 1965 (Box 123, Folder 49)
  - Academic Computer Center, 1969-1970 (Box 123, Folder 50)
  - NYU Admissions, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 333 1
  - Army Reserve Officers' Training Corps, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Commission on Coordinated Liberal Arts Studies, 1968-1970 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Commission on Effective Use of Resources, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Teacher Education, 1968-1970 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Deans Council, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Evaluations, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - NYU Faculty Tenure Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Financial Report, 1967-1968 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation Libertto, 1968-1970 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - NYU Rules Regulating Student Discipline, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Sponsored Research and Training (Monthly Reports), 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Health Services, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - MAT Program, 1968-1970 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - NYU Copies of MAT Program, 1968 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - NYU Off Campus Courses, 1968-1969 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Graduate School of Social Work (Dean Alex Rosen), 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - NYU Governance of NYU (Handbook etc.), 1968-1969 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - NYU Governance of Schools other than NYU, undated (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - University Governance - Student Conduct and Discipline Proceedings, 1968-1969 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - Hatchett Controversy, 1968 (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - Senate Meeting, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 23)
  - Graduate Commission, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 24)
  - Dean's Council, 1968-1969 (Box 124, Folder 25)
  - Report of Committee to Study Faculty-Student Participation, 1967 (Box 124, Folder 26)
  - Birkeland, Birgit E., 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 27)
  - Carlton, Dr. Patrick - Office of Educational Research, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 28)
  - Hug, Dr. Elsie - Graduate Office, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 29)
  - Lion, Professor Paul, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 30)
  - Mininberg, Elliot, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 31)
  - Rowland, Dr. Thomas G., 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 32)
  - Sc. Of Ed. Azzarelli, Dr. Joseph J., 1963-1969 (Box 124, Folder 33)
  - Agnew Memorial, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 34)
  - Faculty Correspondence: R, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 35)
  - School of Education, Baker, Elmer, 1968-1969 (Box 124, Folder 36)
  - President Hester / Union, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 37)
  - President Hester / Cambodia, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 38)
  - President Hester / Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 39)
  - President Hester / Replies for, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 40)
  - Kleinman, Dean Lou, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 41)
  - Berezin, Irving (Vice Presidnet Administrative Affairs), 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 42)
  - Bragdon, Paul E. (VP for Public Affairs), 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 43)
  - de Capriles, Miguel, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 44)
  - Hester / Speeches, 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 45)
  - Whiteman, Dr. Harold B. (V. Chan. For Student Affairs), 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 46)
  - Payne, William F. (VP for Development), 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 47)
  - Roth, Dr. Sidney (Office of Sponsored Research), 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 48)
  - McDonald, Dean Frederick J., 1969-1970 (Box 124, Folder 49)
  - Dill, Dean John R., 1969-1970
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 334 9
  - Sponsored Research and Training (Monthly Reports), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Sponsored Research and Training (Monthly Reports), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Sponsored Research and Training (Monthly Reports), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Sponsored Research and Training (Monthly Reports), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Sponsored Research and Training (Monthly Reports), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Student Involvement, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Student Life Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Student Life Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Students Presidents Council, 1968 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Committee to Study Student Press, 1970 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - NYU Transfer Students (Report on), 1969 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Union Handouts, Flyers, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - University Governance - Student Conduct and Discipline Proceedings, 1968-1969 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - University News (Internal), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - University News (Miscellaneous), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - University Senate, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - University Senate, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - University Senate, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - University Senate, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - University Senate, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - University Senate, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - University Senate Calendar Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 22)
  - NYU/DEG University Scholars, 1964, 1969 (Box 125, Folder 23)
  - University Without Walls (Samuel Baskin), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 24)
  - University Without Walls (Samuel Baskin), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 25)
  - University Without Walls (Samuel Baskin), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 26)
  - Urban Affairs - Special Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 27)
  - Urban Projects - Univ.-Wide Meeting, 1970 (Box 125, Folder 28)
  - Washington Square Center, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 29)
  - Washington Square Evening College re: phasing out, 1967 (Box 125, Folder 30)
  - Whiteman, Dr. Harold B. (V. Chancellor of Student Affairs), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 31)
  - Whiteman, Dr. Harold B. (V. Chancellor of Student Affairs), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 32)
  - Workshop in the Black Experience, 1968 (Box 125, Folder 33)
  - Workshop in the Black Experience, 1968 (Box 125, Folder 34)
  - Associate Dean for Instruction: Replacing Milton Schwebel, 1967-1968 (Box 125, Folder 35)
  - Baum, Vice President Werner A., 1966 (Box 125, Folder 36)
  - Buckler, Dean William E., 1965-1968 (Box 125, Folder 37)
  - Division of Behavioral Sciences, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 38)
  - Gen. Corres. "B", 1962-1967 (Box 125, Folder 39)
  - Gen. Corres. "B", 1962-1967 (Box 125, Folder 40)
  - Gen. Corres. "B", 1967 (Box 125, Folder 41)
  - Gen. Corres. "B", 1968-1969 (Box 125, Folder 42)
  - Gen. Corres. "B", 1970 (Box 125, Folder 43)
  - Birkeland, Birgit E., 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 44)
  - Counselor Education, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 45)
  - Counselor Education, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 46)
  - Deans Heads Memos, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 47)
  - Deans Heads Memos, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 48)
  - Deans Group Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 49)
  - Deans Group Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 50)
  - Deans Group Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 51)
  - Division Heads - Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 52)
  - Doctoral Requirement, Sponsorship, Etc., 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 53)
  - Doctoral Requirement, Sponsorship, Etc., 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 54)
  - Educational Technology Group, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 55)
  - Educational Administration (Formerly Adminstration and Supervision), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 56)
  - Educational Administration (Formerly Administration and Supervision), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 57)
  - Educational Administration (Formerly Administration and Supervision), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 58)
  - Educational Administration (Formerly Administration and Supervision), 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 59)
  - Educational Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 60)
  - English, Speech and Ed. Theatre, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 61)
  - English, Speech and Ed. Theatre, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 62)
  - English, Speech and Ed. Theatre, 1969-1970 (Box 125, Folder 63)
  - Goodwin, Helen D., 1967-1968 (Box 125, Folder 64)
  - Harvey, Dean Ray F., 1965-1966 (Box 125, Folder 65)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 335 6
  - Hester - Annual Reports, 1963 (Box 125, Folder 66)
  - Hester - Commencement Address, 1968 (Box 125, Folder 67)
  - Hug, Dr. Elsie, 1968-1969 (Box 125, Folder 68)
  - Hug, Dr. Elsie, 1967-1970 (Box 125, Folder 69)
  - Hug, Dr. Elsie, 1967-1970 (Box 125, Folder 70)
  - Library File, 1966-1968 (Box 125, Folder 71)
  - Library File, 1966-1968 (Box 125, Folder 72)
  - McDonald, Fredrick J., 1968-1969 (Box 125, Folder 73)
  - School of Ed: Services to the Underprivileged, undated
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968
  - Division of Music Ed, 1969-1970
  - Creative Arts, 1969-1970
  - Associate Dean for Instruction, 1967-1968
  - Doctoral Requirement Sponsorship etc., 1969-1970
  - Birkeland, Birgit E., 1969-1970
  - Counselor Education, 1969-1970
  - Creative Arts, 1969-1970
  - Division of Music Ed, 1969-1970
  - Division Heads - Memos, 1969-1970
  - Educational Technology Group, 1969-1970
  - School of Ed: Mersand Letter Written for President Hester, 1967-1968 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - School of Ed: Jackson, Dr. Fredrick - Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - School of Ed: Kastner, Dean Elwood C., 1965 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - School of Ed: Niles, Chancellor R. (Except Correspondence), 1965-1966 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - School of Ed: Niles: Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - School of Ed: Pollaock, Vice President Thomas, 1965-1966 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Dean Daniel E. Griffiths - Agenda and Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Purchase Orders Pending, undated (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Vita, 1965-1966 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Senate Meeting, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Strike - Kent State, Cambodia, Etc., 1969-1970 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Washington Square Council, 1967-1970 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Urban Affairs, 1965-1967 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Division of Phys. Ed. Health and Recreation, 1967-1970 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 336 4
  - Dr. Arnold Spinner (Center for Field Research), 1968-1970 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Student Activities Invitations Handouts, 1966-1970 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Student Council, 1968-1970 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Student Life, 1967-1968 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Student Participation in Governance, 1968-1969 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Summer Session, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Meeting with Dr. Blustain re: Summer Session, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Student Publications, 1966-1967 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Summer Session, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - School of Ed: Stencils 1-3, 1967-1968 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Summer Session, 1969-1970 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Summer Session, 1972-1975 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Publications: A, undated (Box 128, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 337 2
  - Faculty Publications: B - G, undated (Box 129, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 338 0
  - "Selected Writings", undated (Box 130, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 339 8
  - Faculty Publications: K-Z, undated (Box 131, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 340 6
  - Faculty Publications, undated (Box 132, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 341 4
  - "Selected Writings", undated (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Cue Meetings, undated (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Cue Proposals, undated (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Cue "Materials Sent by Messenger", undated (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Project Proposals (orange cover), undated (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Project Evaluations (yellow cover), undated (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Project Evaluations, undated (Box 133, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 342 2
  - Progress reports, undated (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Mail, undated (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Cue Buffalo Material, undated (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Croft Materials Sent to DEG, undated (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Memos, undated (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, undated (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Budgets, undated (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Fund Raising / School of Education, 1963-1968 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 281 2
  - ESSO Education Foundation, 1964 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - NYU Capitol Campaign Program (Misc. materials), 1967 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Supt. Donovan Mtg - Teacher Corps, 1965 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Proposals Physical Education (Bucher), 1967 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Meeting - Dr. Hollis Moore, 1964 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meeting, 1962 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Commission on Coordinated Liberal Arts Studies, 1962-1966 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Adminstrative Council, 1965 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Commission on Student Life, 1965-1966 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Student Council, 1963-1966 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Student Activities, 1962-1966 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Capitol Program, 1964-1967 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - Gen. Correspondence: K, 1969-1970 (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - Gen. Correspondence: N, 1962-1967 (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - Gen. Correspondence: P, 1963-1969 (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Gen. Correspondence: Q, 1962-1969 (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - Gen. Correspondence: R, 1961-1970 (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - Gen. Correspondence: S, 1965-1969 (Box 134, Folder 19)
  - Gen. Correspondence: S, 1969-1970 (Box 134, Folder 20)
  - Gen. Correspondence: T, 1966-1969 (Box 134, Folder 21)
  - Gen. Correspondence: V, 1966-1970 (Box 134, Folder 22)
  - Gen. Correspondence: W, 1968-1969 (Box 134, Folder 23)
  - Gen. Correspondence: W, 1965-1967 (Box 134, Folder 24)
  - Gen. Correspondence: Z, 1965-1970 (Box 134, Folder 25)
  - Items Distributed to Faculty, 1967-1970 (Box 134, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1967-1968 (Box 134, Folder 27)
  - Graduate Commission, 1967-1969 (Box 134, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Correspondence: R, 1965-1970 (Box 134, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Correspondence: S, 1968-1970 (Box 134, Folder 30)
  - Faculty Council Meetings, 1967-1969 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 282 0
  - Union, 1969-1970 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council - Issues Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Dean Blustain, 1966-1970 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Dean Payne, 1965-1970 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - VP Robinson, 1967-1970 (Box 135, Folder 6)